ZACH Z. WANG

San Francisco, CA • 415-272-6740 • wangzihao-zach@outlook.com • GitHub: zachs-playground.github.io

SKILLS and SUMMARY

Primary Languages: C++, C#, Python, CUDA **Familiar With:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript **Focus Area:** Computer Vision, Deep Learning, Virtual Reality, Reinforcement Learning, Simulation

I have three years of programming experience with various languages. My cross-domain background in business and technology provides me with acute insight into problems and enables me to have a user-oriented mindset. My research experiences can further prove my abilities of identifying problems and proposing viable solutions.

RESEARCH PROJECTS

- 1) Vertex2Image Construct Human Figure Based On A Monocular Video **Published In ACM IUI 2023 Conference**
- 2) 3D Pose Estimation From Multi-View 2D Joints' Locations

Target IEEE Pattern Analysis and Machine Intelligence Journal

WORKING EXPERIENCES

Assistant Manager, Dixon, CA

May 2017 - Present

CP Capital Group Inc.

The company owns several hotel businesses in the Bay Area and operates tourism business for regular travel groups, student groups, and delegation groups.

- develop and maintain company's online group-booking platform for hotel rooms
- establish and maintain relationships with hotels, vendors, and clients, such as Ctrip and Priceline.com
- handle about 20000-room bookings annually

Remote Contractor, Harbin, China

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022

HanMa Cemetery Service LLC

The company provides cemetery services for Muslim communities in China. The business part I involved in is to use the ArcGIS interface to provide tomb locations based on name searches. This is the prototype website: https://www.muditu.com/haerbin/

- train a self-supervised model to generate pseudo labels in their raw image dataset for downstream applications
- design a deep learning model to recognize text information in the images and reduced 76% of the workload for employees
- create an internal tool to increase employees' productivity. The average input time of an employee is reduced from 90 seconds per image to 30 seconds per image

Founding Member, San Francisco, CA

Jan 2021 - Jun 2022

Sci-Bots LLC

The company is a non-profit organization that teaches kids between 6 and 10 years old to learn about micro-controller, programming, and robotics in a fun way. We collaborate with DJI and MG Space to design the curriculum. Our website: www.sci-bots.org

- serve as the main curriculum designer and developed 4 classes
- train lecturers for new class materials every week
- supervise class flow and progress

EDUCATION

Master of Science in Computer Science

Graduated on Dec 2022

San Francisco State University, San Francisco, California

Master of Business Administration

Graduated on Jun 2019

San Francisco State University, San Francisco, California